-嘿  -你好
- Hey. - Hey!
机器人老兄  这边来
Yo robot! Over here!
你好  万圣节愉快
Hello! Happy Halloween!
有什么需要帮忙的
How can I help you?
我不喜欢我的甜点
I didn't like my dessert.
噢不是吧
Oh no!
很难吃吗
Was it bad?
超难吃
Painfully bad.
所以就免单吧  行不
So take it off my bill, would ya?
嗯
Mm!
可是  你都吃光光了啊
But, you ate all of it.
而且你还在舔盘子
And you're licking the plate.
我在舔走悲伤
I'm licking the pain away.
悲伤是什么  能吃吗
I don't understand pain.
嗷
Ow.
现在我懂得了
Now I understand.
嘿
Hey!
我回来了
I'm back.
你去哪了  我还以为你掉厕所里了
Where you been? You were in the bathroom forever.
耶  我想提前练练“不给糖就捣蛋”
Yeah! I decided to start trick or treating early.
在女厕所里吗
In the girls' bathroom?
是呀  我敲了很多隔间门
Uh-huh! I knocked on the stall doors.
好吧  虽然我很怕问你这个  但是你得到什么了
Okay, I'm a little scared to ask this, but what'd ya get?
半卷卫生纸
I got half a roll of toilet paper.
几根牙线
Some dental floss...
还有一把车钥匙
And car keys.
-车钥匙呢  -卫生间地板上呢
- Where are the car keys? - Oh, on the bathroom floor.
那个大妈扔到我脸上  然后反弹掉了
They bounced off my face after the lady threw 'em at me.
-噢  咱们该回家了  -急什么
- Ooh, we gotta go home! - What's the rush?
我得去给你整套新万圣节装扮
Well, I have to get you a new Halloween costume,
而且咱们一点半还要看孩子呢
and we have a babysitting job at one-thirty.
今天还要看孩子
We're babysitting a kid today?!
-是呀  -今天周六啊
- Yeah! - But it's Saturday!
而且是万圣节  你知道大家都叫今天什么吗
And it's Halloween! Do you know what they call that?!
万圣周六啊
Saturween!
三年一度的重大日子啊
It only happens like once every three hundred years!
不是应该七年一度吗
Shouldn't it happen more like, once every seven years?
噢  现在你倒变聪明了
Oh, so all of a sudden you're smart?
咱们只需照看一个小姑娘  从一点半到五点
We only have to babysit one little girl from one-thirty to five,
然后我们就可以享受万圣节美好时光啦
and then we can have all our Halloween fun.
-是万圣周六  -你爱怎么叫就怎么叫吧
- Saturween! - Whatever ween you want!
而且既然今天是节日...
And since today's a holiday...
我不想看孩子
I don't want to babysit.
我们要双份报酬
We're getting paid double!
这我喜欢
I like this plan.
我绝不会在远处
I'm never that far.
无论你在哪儿
No matter where you are.
相信吧  我们可以让它成真
Believe it, we can make it come true.
我们按自己的方式往下做  不管别人怎么说
We'll do it our way, no matter what they say.
因为自己的事情只能自己做
Because no one's gonna do it for you.
而我  我  我  我
But I, I, I, I...
我永远不会说  永不
I'll never say, never.
只要我们在一起
As long as we keep it together.
如果你要实现梦想  也深知梦想的意义
If you're living a dream, and you know what it means.
绝对不要让别人改变你的主意
Then you can't let them change your mind.
这就是我们所选择的生活  持续地打破常规
It's the life that we choose, and we still break the rules.
但一切都会好起来的
But it's all gonna be just fine.
一切都会好起来的
Yeah, we're all gonna be just fine.
我们都会好起来的
You and me we're gonna be just fine.
莎姆和小猫的新生活  第一季第十五集
Sam & Cat S01E15 Doll Sitting
我讨厌这个装扮  我不能穿这个出去见人
I hate this costume. I can't go out in the world like this.
为啥呀
Why not?
因为我看起来像个傻子
Because I look like an idiot.
才不是呢  你看起来和我一样
No. You look just like me.
现在呢...
Now...
你就可以去玩“不给糖就捣蛋”啦
You are ready for some trickin' and some treatin'.
然后人们问我  你扮的是谁啊
And when people ask me "Who are you dressed up as?"
我该说什么呢
What am I supposed to say?
你就说  你好我是瓦伦汀小猫  试试看
You say, "Hi! I'm Cat Valentine". Try it.
你好 我是瓦伦汀小猫试试看
Hi I'm Cat Valentine try it.
不对  你应该像我一样说
No, you're supposed to say it like me.
好吧...
Okay, uh...
你好
Hi!
我是瓦伦汀小猫
I'm Cat Valentine!
我老在白痴的事情上犯二
Simple things confuse me.
叮咚
Ding dong.
-你学我叮咚啦  -什么叮咚
- You did my doorbell thing. - What doorbell thing?
好诡异
This is weird.
-我去开门  -那我就追随你
- I'll get the door. - I'll trail after you.
你好
Hi.
你好...老娘放弃了  有事吗
Hi... I can't do it. 'Sup?
我是德兰芝先生
My name is Mister Drange.
这里是...
Is this...
莎姆与小猫的狂拽酷炫叼炸天...
Sam and Cat's super rocking fun-time...
宝贝看护服务吗
Babysitting Service?
没错
Yep.
靠边站
Stand aside.
那么 你托我们照看的孩子呢
So, where is the kid you want us to babysit?
她在走廊等着呢
She's out in the hallway.
进来吧  克拉丽斯
Come, Clarice.
她很害羞
She's shy.
我去把她取来
I'll fetch her.
你在哪找到这个大叔的
Where did you find this guy?
-花店  -噢
- At a flower shop. - Oh.
-就在墓地旁边  -啊
- By a graveyard. - Ah.
这是我女儿  克拉丽斯
This is my daughter, Clarice.
克拉丽斯  这是莎姆和小猫
Clarice, meet Sam and Cat.
-嘿 -嗨
- Hey. - Hi.
你说什么
What's that, Clarice?
噢不  他们不是双胞胎  要真是那样就好了
No. They're not twins. But wouldn't that be precious?
呃...
Uh...
我还以为你要让我们照看你的女儿呢
I thought you wanted us to babysit your daughter.
没错啊
Indeed, I do.
小猫  小心点替我抱她一下
Cat, would you hold her carefully for a moment?
这是注意事项
Here's a list of instructions
你要按上面说的照顾克拉丽斯
you'll need to follow as you look after Clarice.
你就让我们按着上面说的照顾...
Uh, this is a list of things you want us to do...
这玩意儿
For that.
照顾她 是的
For her. Yes.
请大声读出来
Please read it out loud.
轮流念
Taking turns.
“别把克拉丽斯弄脏”
"Do not let Clarice become filthy".
“万一她弄脏了 你们要给她洗澡”
"But if she does become filthy, you must bathe her".
她超爱洗澡
She enjoys the bath.
你给我们双倍报酬  对吧
You're paying us double, right?
当然
Certainly.
好了  看看我的怀表  是时候离开了
Well, according to my pocket watch, it's time for me to take my leave.
克拉丽斯...
Clarice...
老爸爱你
Daddy loves you.
那个大叔太吓人啦
That man is so freaky!
-老爸爱你  -别这样
- Daddy loves you. - Don't!
-老爸爱你  -莎姆你住口
- Daddy loves you. - Sam! Don't.
-来爸爸这边吧  -雅蠛蝶啊
- Come to Daddy. - I don't wanna!
好了克拉丽斯  我准备了大南瓜给你雕  另一个给莎姆
Okay Clarice, I got a big pumpkin for you to carve, one for Sam.
我就要...
And for me...
一个长残的小南瓜
A pumpkinette!
-小猫  -啊
- Cat. - Aah!
你干什么呢
What are you doing?
准备咱们一起和克拉丽斯一起雕南瓜啊
Setting up pumpkins for us to carve with Clarice.
那就是个娃娃 不是真的 你看...
It's a doll. It's not real, see...?
她感觉不到疼
It doesn't feel pain.
啥也闻不到
It can't sniff!
所以我们不能和她一起雕南瓜
And we're not carving pumpkins with it.
啊
Ah!
万圣节快乐哟  女巫们
Happy Halloween, witches!
-你好啊戴斯  -嘿
- Hi Dice. - Hey yo.
哇哦莎姆 你和小猫简直一模一样
Whoa, Sam! You look just like Cat.
我不在意  给我来个泡菜
I don't care and I want a pickle.
那么  这位漂亮小精灵...
So, for the pretty genie...
是在说我吗
I think that's me.
我给你带了
We got...
-一个精灵瓶  -好耶
- A genie bottle. - Yay!
然后为了你能扮的更像精灵...
And to complete your whole "Genie thing" A very old book...
一本咒语书
Of magic spells.
耶
Yay!
这些咒语都是真的吗
Are these spells real?!
呃是啊 当然啦
Oh yeah, sure.
嘿  你应该也给我带点东西来的
Hey, you're supposed to bring me something ya know.
噢对啦  你的糖果
Oh yeah, your candy.
噢对啦  我的糖果
Oh yeah, my candy.
什么糖果
What candy?
地球上最酸的糖果
The most sour candy on Planet Earth.
-超级酸嘴巴  -我以为那是违法的呢
- Super Puckers. - I thought those were illegal.
没错  可是哥上面有人
They are. I know a guy.
呃  我等不及把那糖
Ugh! I can't wait to give
给那帮熊孩子们吃 然后看他们...
that candy out to kids and watch 'em go all...
啊 啊
Ah! Ah!
妈咪  我的嘴
Mommy! My mouth!
酸死我啦
It's so sour!
啊
Ah!
耶  这就是万圣节精神
Yeah, that's the Halloween spirit.
给我糖 快点
Candy! Now!
我落在家里了...我这就去取来
I left it at my place... I'll go grab it!
-等等等一下... -怎么了
- Wait wait wait wait... - What?
你走之前 我能试试上面的咒语吗
Before you go, can I please try a spell on you?
你快放这孩子回去取糖
Will ya let the child go get my candy?
等我念完咒语
After my spell!
-快点  -好哒
- Hurry. - Kay-Kay.
“唛哩唛哩轰”
"Eeeklawokka, eeka lokka rop-chok"...
唛哩轰
Rop-chok?
“给我一个野兽..
"A beast for me...
你将会变成野兽”
"A beast you'll be!
嘿哈
Y'chaaaa!"
Y'chaaaa!
这本书真垃圾
This book is garbage.
-快给老娘去取糖  -去去就回
- Go get my candy. - Back in a sec.
嘿 你确定不和我去“不给糖就捣蛋”吗
Hey, you sure you don't want to go trick or treating with me?
没门
No way.
我要呆在家里  分酸糖给熊孩子们
I'm staying home, passing out Super Puckers,
延续我从5岁之后每年万圣节的传统
and doing the same thing I've done every Halloween since I was five years old.
什么
What?
我做一个装满辣椒的大南瓜...
I fill a big pumpkin with chili...
嗯哼
Yeah?
-然后我吃掉辣椒  -啊哈
- Then I eat the chili... - Uh huh?
然后我解开裤子看电视
Then I unbutton my pants and watch TV.
哦莎姆  你真坏
Oh Sam. You're so damaged.
耶  是戴斯回来了  门开着呢
Oh yeah, Dice is back. It's open!
我说  门开着呢
I say, it's open!
他怎么不进来呢
Why won't he just come in?
不晓得  我也困惑了
I dunno, but it's wazzin' me off.
啊
Ah!
莎姆  我的咒语应验了
Sam! My spell!
我把戴斯变成了一只猴子
I turned Dice into a monkey!
是啊  他还带来了我的糖
Yeah, and he brought my candy.
谢啦孩子
Thanks, kid.
莎姆
Sam.
等一下猴子戴斯  别跑啊
Wait, monkey-Dice! Don't run away.
莎姆  你看见了吗
Sam, did you see that?!?!
-我看见了一只猴子  -那本来是戴斯
- I saw a monkey. - That was Dice!
胡说
Shut up.
我是认真的  你看
Sam, I'm serious! Look!
我施的这条咒语...
This spell I did...
是把人变成野兽的
Was to turn a human person into a beast!
而且猴子算野兽
And a monkey is a beast!
有没有一条咒语能帮我妈找到工作的
Is there a spell in there that'll turn my mom into a woman with a job?
我很认真的
This is serious!
你得帮我把猴子戴斯捉住
You have to help me get monkey-Dice
好把他变回男孩
back so I can turn him back into a real boy!
你淡定些好吗
Will you chill your chaz?
世界上没有真正的魔法
There's no such thing as real magic, all right?
你没把戴斯变成猴子  还有
You didn't turn Dice into a monkey. And oh, by the way...
娃娃是不会自己就把南瓜刻成南瓜灯的
Little girly dolls cannot just carve pumpkins into jack-o-lan...
-哦  但  -啊
- Oh b... - Ah!
还是不相信呢魔法吗
Still don't believe in real magic?!
不信
No...
但以防万一
But just in case...
还是把刀从她手里拿走吧
I'm taking the knife away from the doll.
是谁刻的南瓜
Who carved that pumpkin?
告诉我
Tell me!
我竟然在和娃娃说话
Ah, I'm talking to a doll.
我看着像小猫  现在行为都不正常了
I look like Cat and now I'm acting like a ding-bat.
肯定是这身行头弄的
I guess that makes sense.
莎姆  莎姆  我们怎么办
Sam! Sam, what are we gonna do?!
-怎么了  -戴斯  他在我们房间
- About what? - Dice! He's in our room.
-他还是只猴子  -小猫
- And he's still a monkey! - Cat...
我施了3个变回人类的咒语
I tried three different
没有一个有用
change-back spells and none of them worked.
他就坐在你床上
He's back there, just sitting on your bed.
那只猴子不是戴斯  我得告诉你多少次
That monkey isn't Dice! How many times do I...
嗯  他在我床上
Mm! He's on my bed?
嗯
Yeah.
它可能在上面干了点坏事
And he might have done something bad on it.
它在我床上大便了
That monkey pooped in my bed?!
我们就叫它猴子方便了一下吧
Let's just call it "Monkey business".
啊  该死
Ah! Dang it!
万圣节不应该是这样的
This is not how Halloween should be!
我手机呢
Where's my phone?!
我在猜莎姆在给谁打电话
I wonder who Sam is calling.
我在给戴斯打  所以你就能和他通话
I'm calling Dice so you can talk to him and he can
这就能解释清他还是个孩子  不是只猴子
explain to you that he's still a kid, not a monkey.
像是戴斯手机的声音
That sounds like Dice's phone.
天呐
Oh my gosh.
把娃娃放台子上  跟我来
Put the doll on the counter and come with me.
-我们马上回来  -她是个娃娃  不要和她说话
- We'll be right back. - It's a doll, don't talk to it!
好吧
All right.
为什么这只猴子拿着戴斯的手机
Why is that monkey holding Dice's Pear Phone?
这只猴子就是戴斯  我告诉你
That monkey is Dice, I tell ya!
不是
It's not Dice!
就是  我把他变成了野兽了
Is so! I turned him into a beast!
-等下  别跑  -它为什么变这样了
- Wait, no! - Why's he looking like that?
等下  戴斯  不要跑
Wait! Dice, don't leave!
我得把你变回小男孩
I have to turn you back into a young boy!
赶紧回来把你的方便产物解决掉啊
Oh, get back here and clean up your monkey business!
-什么声音  -快走
- What was that? - Come on!
哦  猴子戴斯跑走了
Oh! Monkey-Dice ran away!
不关心  我想知道是谁尖叫了
I don't care. I wanna know who screamed.
啊  电视而已
Ah, it was just the TV.
哦
Oh.
等下
Wait...
谁把电视打开的
Who turned on the TV?
哦天呐
Oh my!
-你看见了吗  -不  我的眼睛是闭着的
- You see this? - No, my eyes are closed.
-看  -我不想看
- Look. - I don't wanna!
-不行  -啊
- Mm! - Ah!
-啊  -啊
- Ah! - Ah!
好了  好了  我想知道
Okay! Okay! I wanna know how
那个娃娃是怎么从那个台子到这个沙发上的
that doll got from that counter to this couch!
还开了电视
And turned on the TV!
还做了微波炉爆米花
And made microwave popcorn!
我都不知道怎么做
Even I don't know how to make microwave popcorn!
就是说啊
I know!
-啊  -叮咚
- Ah! - Ding dong!
好了  她爹来了
Good. Her "Father's" Here.
快
Hurry.
我来接克拉丽斯了
I've returned for Clarice.
给你
Here ya go.
啊  我的宝贝
Ah, there's my precious.
希望她没有很淘气
I hope she wasn't naughty.
没有  她很听话  你们什么时候想走都行
No, she was great, well, you guys can leave anytime
现在就挺好  万圣节快乐  拜
you want like right now happy Halloween see you bye.
等下
Wait.
他还是得付钱  双份
He still has to pay us... double.
当然  除非
Certainly. Unless...
除非什么
Unless what?
你们想再多赚些钱
Would you girls like to earn some more money, and enjoy some...
享受些音乐吗
Music?
什么  音乐
What... "Music"?
我手里有三张
I have three tickets in my hand.
演唱会的门票
To a concert.
-德・欧米茄  -我爱德・欧米茄
- Del Deville?!?! - I love Del Deville!
八区  这些票太赞了
Section eight?! These tickets are amazing!
是不是太美好了
Aren't they just to die for?
是啊  什么
Yeah! What?!
如果你们带着克拉丽丝一块去
You girls may have those tickets...
这些票就是你们的了
If you take Clarice with you.
开个小会
Sidebar?
我可以允许
I'll allow it.
-你想怎么办  -我想去看德・欧米茄
- What do you wanna do?! - I wanna see Del Deville!
-我也是  -我不想带着这个吓人的娃娃
- Me, too! - I don't wanna take that creepy doll!
他不会知道我们带没带的
He's not gonna know if we take the doll or not!
-我们不能撒谎  -今天万圣节  可以的
- We can't fib! - Yeah, we can. It's Halloween!
哦对  我忘记了
Ooh yeah, I forgot!
好  我们同意
Okay, we're in.
-有一个条件  -话真多
- One thing. - Blah.
你们必须照张克莱里斯在演唱会
You must take a photograph of Clarice at the concert...
享受的照片
Enjoying herself.
开个小会
Sidebar?
-我还是想去  -我也是
- I still wanna go! - Me, too!
-我们同意  -非常好
- We'll do it! - Splendid.
我确定克莱里斯今晚会非常
I'm sure that Clarice will have a wonderful...
戴斯回来了
Dice is back.
不好意思  那不是真的猴子
Excuse me, but that isn't really a monkey so I
我得把他变回小男孩了
have to go change him back into a young boy.
戴斯
Dice!
别再当猴子了
Stop being a monkey!
她好奇怪啊
She's rather strange.
可不是嘛
Isn't she?
呜
Woo!
宝贝我是风流浪子
Baby, I'm bad enough.
对你我无限风流
Bad enough for you.
呜
Whooo...
Whoh...
好啦
All right!
娃娃不错嘛
Hey. Nice doll.
你们总是带娃娃去演唱会吗
You girls always bring your dolly to concerts?!
给吉他手杰克逊・贝尔些掌声
Give some love to Jackson Bell on guitar!
-哦  我的脸  -快走
- Ow! My face! - Go! Go!
快滚
Blah!
万圣香肠节快乐
Happy hallo-weiner!
说得好啊
That was clever.
下一首歌是我们的最新单曲
This next song is our latest single.
你们知道是什么  一起唱  开始
You know it, sing along. Go!
哦  我们大爱这首歌
Oh, we love this song.
不知怎么你的声音还在我的耳边
Somehow you're still in my ear.
你的双眸还清晰地出现在我的眼前
Those eyes I see them so clear.
它们似乎在向我诉说
your eyes are telling me that...
呜
Woo!
-克拉丽丝  -哦耶
- Clarice. - Oh, yeah.
嘿嘿  停下
Hey! Hey, stop the music!
停下  等下等下
Stop the music, hold up, hold up...
-怎么了  -不知道啊
- What's happening? - I dunno.
灯光
Lighting! Lighting,
给8区一束光
gimme a spotlight on section eight, over there.
来束追光
Gimme a spot.
看到了吗  就在那儿
See that? Right there.
又是那个吓人的娃娃
It's that creepy doll!
克拉丽丝
Clarice.
啊天哪
Ah jeez.
-嘿  兄弟别紧张  -不不  我没法不紧张
- Hey man, calm down. - No no, I'm not gonna calm down!
每次我开演唱会都有那个娃娃  我已经受不了了
Every time I do a concert, that dang doll shows up and it's freaking me out!
啊
Uh...
嘿  那个红头发的  你怎么把娃娃带来了
Hey, you with the red hair. Why'd you bring that doll?
莎姆
Sam!
保安  保安
Security! Security!
把那两个女孩和那个娃娃赶出去
Get those girls and that doll outta my concert!
赶出去
Get 'em out!
赶出去  赶出去
Yeah? Yeah!?
-不是吧  -有没有搞错
- Really? - Really?
-哦  你把我的手肘弄疼了  -轻点
- Ow, you're hurting my elbow! - Oh, come on!
抱歉了  洛杉矶
I'm sorry, Los Angeles!
哦
Oh!
最烂的演唱会了
Worst concert ever.
那个保安夹到我的手肘了
That Security man squeezed my elbow.
-嘿  戴斯  -你们好
- Hey! Yo Dice. - Oh, hey, guys.
啊
Ah!
要有多丧心病狂才会在万圣节给孩子葡萄干
What kind of cruel grownup gives a kid raisins on Halloween?
你是个真的男孩
You're... you're a real boy!
什么
Humma?
肯定是我的恢复咒语成功了
One of my change-back spells must've worked!
你又变回小男孩了
You're a boy again!
-她在胡言乱语些什么  -啊  小猫以为
- What's she yammin' about? - Ah, Cat thought that...
-是我们家的马桶声吗  -谁在那
- Was that our toilet? - Who's here?
哦
Oh!
啊
Uh!
看到了吧  我告诉你了它不是戴斯
See?! I told ya the monkey wasn't Dice,
而且根本没有魔法这回事
and that there's no such thing as magic.
啊哈
Uh-huh.
那还猴子是哪来的
Wh... where did that monkey come from?
-它叫法兹  -谁是法兹
- That's Futz. - Who's Futz?!
我姑姑的帮手猴
My Aunt Ferjeen's helper monkey.
它都帮她干什么
What does the monkey help her do?
-吃饭  穿衣  洗澡  -不需再说
- Eat, get dressed, wash. - I've heard enough.
但你怎么把你姑姑的帮手带来了呢
But, why'd you send your Aunt's helper monkey here?
来给莎姆带糖来啊
To bring Sam her candy.
但  它怎么会有你的手机呢
But... but why does he have your cell phone?
什么  是我的手机吗
What?! That's my cell phone...
我以为我弄丢了
I thought I lost it!
法兹  赶快把我的手机给我
Futz, you gimme my phone right now!
噢
Aw!
他把我的电话本都删除了
He deleted all my contacts!
法兹
Futz!
走吧
Let's go.
你要帮我重新输入所有联系人
You are gonna help me re-input every one of my contacts.
我以为我会魔法了呢
I thought I did magic.
抱歉了  孩子
Sorry, kid.
此生无魔法
Ain't no magic in this life.
你们好  是我  德兰芝先生
Hello, it's me, Mr. Drange.
我刚看到一个男孩背着一个猴子
I just saw a monkey riding on a boy's back.
让我想起了我的童年
It reminded me of my childhood.
我猜您可能没结婚吧
I'm guessing there's no Mrs. Drange.
克莱里斯在这儿啊
Ah, there's my Clarice.
演唱会玩得开心吗  亲爱的
Did you enjoy the concert, my sweet?
好啦  别装了
Alright, knock it off!
-悠着点  -这是个娃娃
- Easy. - That is a doll!
她听不见你说话  也不会回答你的
She can't hear you and she can't talk back!
就别假装她是你的女儿
So quit pretending she's your
因为实在是太吓人了
daughter because you're freaking everybody out!
这个
Well.
我看我们不受欢迎了
I can see we're not welcome here.
我的怀表已经过了睡觉时间了
And my pocket watch tells me it's past our bedtime.
来吧  克拉丽丝
Come along, Clarice.
-好的  爸爸  -啊
- Yes, Daddy. - Aah!
谢谢  我玩得很开心
Thanks, I had fun!
万圣节快乐
Happy Halloween.
这年代了谁用怀表啊
Who uses a pocket watch?
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录 www.Deefun.com
■
翻译： Eiley  Pixielee
后期  校订： line  liloelva